[{"answer": "Hi, Lisa.  How was your weekend", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": "", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Hey, John.  It was pretty good", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 17, "question": "Hi, Lisa.  How was your weekend", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Whatd you do", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Hey, John.  It was pretty good", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " My husband and I saw the new Spiderman flick", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Whatd you do", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Oh yeah?  I heard it was awesome.  Did you like it", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " My husband and I saw the new Spiderman flick", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " It was pretty good.  I think my husband liked it more than me.  I guess its kind of ", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Oh yeah?  I heard it was awesome.  Did you like it", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Yeah, I can see that", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 25, "question": " It was pretty good.  I think my husband liked it more than me.  I guess its kind of ", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " What were you up to this weekend", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Yeah, I can see that", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Oh, nothing too exciting.    I still have tons of work to do in the new house ", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 30, "question": " What were you up to this weekend", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Thats cool.  It was so hot and humid this weekend.  I hope you werent doing to", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Oh, nothing too exciting.    I still have tons of work to do in the new house ", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Tell me about it.  I actually had a lot to do on the outside of the house, so I wa", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Thats cool.  It was so hot and humid this weekend.  I hope you werent doing to", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " The joys of home ownership", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Tell me about it.  I actually had a lot to do on the outside of the house, so I wa", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Hey, did you hear that Paris Hilton got out of jail", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 43, "question": " The joys of home ownership", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Yes, that whole story is so crazy", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Hey, did you hear that Paris Hilton got out of jail", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Hi!  Im Tammy.  I just started here in the office today", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Yes, that whole story is so crazy", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Hi, Tammy.  Im Lisa, and this is John.  We both work in Human Resources here", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Hi!  Im Tammy.  I just started here in the office today", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Nice to meet you, Tammy", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Hi, Tammy.  Im Lisa, and this is John.  We both work in Human Resources here", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " This office seems pretty great.  Can I ask you a question though?  Im not sur", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Nice to meet you, Tammy", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Ummmmmmm", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 52, "question": " This office seems pretty great.  Can I ask you a question though?  Im not sur", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Well, you know everyone earns a different amount based on education", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Ummmmmmm", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Oh, I see.  So, do you guys live near the office", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Well, you know everyone earns a different amount based on education", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " I rent a place thats just about 10 minutes away", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Oh, I see.  So, do you guys live near the office", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Thats convenient", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 58, "question": " I rent a place thats just about 10 minutes away", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Thats convenient", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I just bought a house a month ago thats about 15 minutes away", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Yeah", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Oh my god!  I have been wanting to buy a house.  How much did you pay fo", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 61, "question": " I just bought a house a month ago thats about 15 minutes away", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " What", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Oh my god!  I have been wanting to buy a house.  How much did you pay fo", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " How much did you pay for your house?  What do you pay each month for you", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 64, "question": " What", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Umm, Id rather not say.  Its kind of personal", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 72, "question": " How much did you pay for your house?  What do you pay each month for you", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Oh, OK.  Sorry", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Umm, Id rather not say.  Its kind of personal", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Tammy, what department do you work in", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Oh, OK.  Sorry", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Im in the sales department", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Tammy, what department do you work in", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Do you think youll like the new position", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Im in the sales department", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Hopefully.  The first day is always a bit overwhelming, but I think Im going t", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Do you think youll like the new position", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " OK, well see you later", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Hopefully.  The first day is always a bit overwhelming, but I think Im going t", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Nice meeting you", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 82, "question": " OK, well see you later", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Nice meeting you", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Wow!  What was up with her?  She was asking all kinds of personal questions", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Bye", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " I know.  What a weirdo.  I cant believe she asked how much you pay each mont", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Wow!  What was up with her?  She was asking all kinds of personal questions", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Maybe she was just nervous", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 92, "question": " I know.  What a weirdo.  I cant believe she asked how much you pay each mont", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Who knows", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Maybe she was just nervous", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Well, I hope she doesnt talk like that with everyone here.  Some people coul", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Who knows", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " I guess I better get back to work too", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Well, I hope she doesnt talk like that with everyone here.  Some people coul", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Yeah, me too.  Ill see ya around", "docId": "01-06", "aSentId": 99, "question": " I guess I better get back to work too", "qSentId": 98}]
